<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">LTE OnOff</string>
    <string name="license">Copyright (c) 2011, Cunning Logic\nAll rights reserved.\n\nChicken Dance License v0.1\nhttp://supertunaman.com/cdl/\n\nRedistribution and use in source and binary forms, with \nor without modification, are permitted provided that the \nfollowing conditions are met:\n\n    1. Redistributions of source code must retain the \n        above copyright notice, this list of conditions and \n        the following disclaimer.\n    2. Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the \n        above copyright notice, this list of conditions and \n        the following disclaimer in the documentation and/or \n        other materials provided with the distribution.\n    3. Neither the name of the CUNNIN GLOGIC nor the names \n        of its contributors may be used to endorse or promote \n        products derived from this software without specific \n        prior written permission.\n    4. An entity wishing to redistribute in binary form or \n        include this software in their product without \n        redistribution of this software\'s source code with the \n        product must also submit to these conditions where \n        applicable: \n            * For every thousand (1000) units distributed, at \n                least half of the employees or persons \n                affiliated with the product must listen to the \n                "Der Ententanz" (AKA "The Chicken Dance") as \n                composed by Werner Thomas for no less than two \n                (2) minutes\n            * For every twenty-thousand (20000) units distributed, \n                two (2) or more persons affiliated with the entity \n                must be recorded performing the full Chicken Dance, \n                in an original video at the entity\'s own expense,\n                and a video encoded in OGG Theora format, at least \n                three (3) minutes in length, must be submitted to \n                Cunning Logic, provided Cunning Logics\'s contact\n                information. The dance must be based upon the\n                instructions on how to do the Chicken Dance that\n                you should have received with this software. If\n                you have not received instructions on how to do the\n                Chicken Dance, then the dance must be chicken-like\n                in nature.\n            * Any employee or person affiliated with the product \n                must be prohibited from saying the word "plinth" in \n                public at all times, as long as distribution of the \n                product continues. \n\nTHIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS \n"AS IS" AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT \nLIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS \nFOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE \nCOPYRIGHT HOLDER OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, \nINCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, \nBUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; \nLOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER \nCAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT \nLIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN \nANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE \nPOSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE. CUNNING ACCEPTS NO LIABILITY FOR\nANY INJURIES OR EXPENSES SUSTAINED IN THE ACT OF FULFILLING ANY OF \nTHE ABOVE TERMS AND CONDITIONS, ACCIDENTAL OR OTHERWISE.\n</string>
</resources>
